quiztron.com 2016-11-29

# Privacy Policy at Quiztron

Quiztron Online Privacy Policy 

Quiztron takes great pride in utilizing state-of-the-art security procedures. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our Web site. This policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically. 

This policy will let you know: 

1\. What personally identifiable information is collected from you and how it is used;   
2\. Who is collecting your information and with whom may your information be shared;   
3\. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use, and distribution of your information;   
4\. How Quiztron protects your personal information;   
5\. How you can access, update or delete your information;   
6\. What cookies are and how they are used; and   
7\. What else you should know about your online privacy.   

1\. What personal information does Quiztron collect from you and how is it used? 

Quiztron may collect information in several ways from different parts of our Web site. Some personal information may be gathered when you register. During registration, Quiztron asks you to create a user ID and password, email (optional) and certain other personal information. The more information you volunteer (and the more accurate it is), the better we are able to customize your experience. In addition to registration, we may ask you for personal information at other times, including, but not limited to, (a) when you enter a prize giveaway, test, sweepstakes, contest or promotion sponsored by Quiztron and/or our many partners, or (b) should the occasion arise, if and when you make a purchase using Quiztron. If you contact Quiztron, we may keep a record of that correspondence. Quiztron also occasionally asks users to complete surveys that we use for internal research. Wherever Quiztron collects personal information we make an effort to include a link to this Privacy Policy on that page.   
Quiztron`s primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with a customized experience on our Web site. This includes personalized services, interactive communications, possibly even online shopping, and many other types of services. In order to provide services free of charge, we display advertisements. By knowing a little about you, Quiztron is able to deliver more relevant advertisements, content and better service to you. 

Quiztron does internal research on our users-- demographics, interests, and behavior based on the information provided to us upon registration, during a promotion, or from our server log files. We do this to better understand and serve our users. This research is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis. 

2\. Who is collecting your information and with whom may your information be shared? 

Information recorded during your use of Quiztron is kept strictly confidential to Quiztron. As a general rule, Quiztron will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information except when we have your permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or under the circumstances described below. Its sole use is to facilitate your use of Quiztron’s Website. For example, some Quiztron services may be offered in conjunction with a partner company. In order to provide this co-branded service to you, it may be necessary for us to share your personal information with our partner company. If data is being collected and/or maintained by any company other than Quiztron, you will be notified prior to the time of the data collection or transfer. If you do not want your data to be shared, you can choose not to allow the transfer by not using that particular service. 

Promotions that run on Quiztron may be sponsored by companies other than Quiztron or may be co-sponsored by Quiztron and another company. Some or all of the data collected during a promotion may be shared with the sponsor. If data will be shared, you will be notified prior to the time of data collection or transfer. You can decide not to participate in the promotion, if you don’t want your data to be shared. 

If you make a purchase from a store which may be hosted by Quiztron or another merchant, the information obtained during your visit to those stores, and the information you give such as your credit card number and contact information, is provided to the merchants. This is to enable transactions to take place. 

Under confidentiality agreements, Quiztron may match user information with third party data. Also, Quiztron discloses aggregated user statistics (for example, % of our users are female) in order to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers, and other third parties, and for other lawful purposes. Please be aware that Quiztron advertisers or Web sites that have links on our site may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of those Web sites linked to Quiztron are not covered by this privacy statement. 

Quiztron may also disclose user information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) Quiztron=s rights or property, other Quiztron users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. Quiztron may also disclose user information that we deem necessary to maintain and improve our products and services. 

3\. What are my choices regarding collection, use, and distribution of my information? 

If you indicated upon registration that you are interested in receiving offers or information from Quiztron and our partners, we may occasionally send you e-mail about our products and services that we feel may be of interest to you. Only Quiztron (or agents working on behalf of Quiztron and under confidentiality agreements) will send you these direct mailings and only if you indicated that you do not object to these offers. If you do not want to receive such mailings, simply tell us when you give us your personal information. Quiztron does not sell or rent user information to anyone. We will notify you at the time of data collection or transfer if your data will be shared with a third party and you will always have the option of not permitting the transfer. If you do not wish to allow your data to be shared, you can choose not to use a particular service or not to participate in certain promotions or contests. 

4\. How does Quiztron protect my personal information? 

Keeping your personal information private is very important to us. Knowing that you use certain services or features may help us to offer you better and more relevant content, services and advertisements. But as with all personally identifiable information, we do not make this available to any third parties without your permission. Any user statistics that we may provide to prospective advertisers or partners are provided in the aggregate only and do not include any personally identifiable information about any individual user. Please note that there may be several places on the Quiztron Web site where you can transmit credit card information in order to complete a purchase transaction or for verification purposes. Any time we ask for a credit card number we transmit that credit card number in an encrypted format. We use industry-standard, SSL (secure socket layer) encryption. 

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. While we strive to protect your personal information, Quiztron cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. 

5\. What is Quiztron's policy on allowing me to update, correct, or delete my personally identifiable information? 

You may edit any personal information entered with Quiztron at any time by using your Quiztron [password]. If you have forgotten your password, it can be retrieved by clicking the forgot password link. 

6\. What are cookies and how does Quiztron use them? 

As part of offering and providing customizable and personalized services, Quiztron uses cookies to store and sometimes track information about you. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer=s hard drive. All sites on Quiztron where you are prompted to log-in or that are customizable require that you accept cookies. 

Cookies are used by Quiztron to (a) remind us of who you are and to access your account information in order to deliver to you a better and more personalized service; (b) assist merchants to track visits to and business at their stores, and to process the items purchased by you; and (c) measure certain traffic patterns, which areas of Quiztron’s Web site you have visited, and your visiting patterns in the aggregate. This cookie is set when you register or `Sign In` and is modified when you `Sign Out` of our services. This information collected by cookies is sometimes called `clickstream` or `click trail` and may also describe which pages you have seen in each merchant’s store. We use this research to understand how our users= habits are similar or different from one another so that we can make each new experience on Quiztron a better one. We may use this information to better personalize the content, banners, and promotions that you and other users will see on our sites. You also have choices with respect to cookies. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. If you choose to reject all cookies you will be unable to use those Quiztron services that require registration in order to participate. 

7\. What else should I know about my privacy? 

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example on message boards, through email, or in chat areas - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you=re online. You should be aware that when you are on Quiztron`s Web site, you could be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. There are links to other Web sites from Quiztron and all of its subsites that take you outside our service. For example, if you click on a banner advertisement or a Quiztron search result, the click takes you off the Quiztron Web site. This includes links from advertisers, sponsors, and partners that may use Quiztron=s logos as part of a co-branding agreement. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, or otherwise collect data or solicit personal information. Always be aware of where you end up. Please keep in mind that whenever you give out personal information online - for example, via message boards or chat - that information can be collected and used by people you don=t know. While Quiztron strives to protect its users= personal information and privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online, and you do so at your own risk. 

Your Acceptance to These Terms 

By using this Web site, you signify your assent to the Quiztron online privacy policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Web sites. Your continued use of the Quiztron Web sites following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept these changes. 

Additional Information. 

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to Quiztron. 

Policies for Individuals Under 13 Quiztron encourages parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate in the interactive activities offered on the sites. No information should be posted or submitted to Quiztron`s Web site by guests under 13 years of age without the consent of their parent or guardian. 

Unless otherwise disclosed during collection, Quiztron does not provide any personally identifying information, regardless of its source, to any third party for any purpose whatsoever. No information collected from guests under 13 years of age is used for any marketing or promotional purposes whatsoever, either inside or outside Quiztron. 

All registrants receive e-mail confirming their registration. In addition, when a guest under 13 registers, his/her parent or guardian receives an e-mail communicating that registration as well as instructions on how the parent or guardian could delete the registration if so desired. 

Although guests under 13 years of age may be allowed to participate in contests, if such a guest wins, notification and prizes are sent to the parents or guardians identified in the initial registration process. 

Guests` e-mail addresses are only posted on Quiztron’s Web site with the consent of the member. 

Policies for Individuals 13 Years of Age or Older 

With the permission of a guest who is 13 years of age or over, information submitted at the time of registration may be used for marketing and promotional purposes by Quiztron and may be shared with our business partners or companies that have been prescreened by Quiztron. If a guest objects to such use for any reason, he/she may stop that use -- either by e-mail request or by modifying his/her registration information online. Once you have registered with Quiztron, every effort will be made to maintain your information in a secure environment by Quiztron.
